# AYINDE OLUWATOSIN SAMUEL

3, Oluwole Street, Joke-Ayo, Lagos state. 08160884797

Samstringz98@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

A skilled frontend and Mobile developer. I am well-versed in all stages of advanced web development including user interface design, testing and debugging processes. My expertise extends to a range of technologies, including Javascript, Typescript, React, React Native and Angular. I am confident in contributing to projects requiring exceptional attention to detail and passion for crafting user experience.

#### **COMPETENCIES**

Attention to details and accuracy; Good Communication skills; Ability to work under pressure; Ability to change and embrace new idea; Stress tolerance; Ability to work under little or no supervision.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

**Nationality** Nigerian **State of Origin** Ogun

**Local Govt.** Obafemi Owode

**Gender** Male **Marital Status** Single

**Birth Date** 13<sup>th</sup> February, 1998

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

1. May.2013 – June 2015

Orelope Computer Center 289, Old Abeokuta Motor Rd, Agege, Lagos.

Post Held: Personal Assistant Main Responsibility

- Computer Organization and assembly Language
- ❖ Data Entry using Microsoft Office
- Graphics Design using Corel-Draw

2. Sep.2018 – Jan.2019 Student Industrial Work Experience Scheme (SIWES)

**Under The Supervision of A Non-Governmental** 

**Organization** 

**Known As Orelope Computer Center,** 

Lagos state.

## **Main Responsibilities**:

Effective use of:

- **\*** MICROSOFT OFFICE PACKAGES
- **❖** COREL-DRAW
- **\*** ADOBE PHOTOSHOP
- 3. 2021-2022

Beyond The Visual (BTV)
Front End Development (Intern)

#### **Main Responsibilities**

- ❖ Worked on a multi-storefront web application using React
- ❖ Worked with fellow front-end developers on the team to create a great user experience.
- ❖ Followed policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times.
- 4. 2023-2024

D-Degree Digitial Hub Front End Development (Junior Dev)

#### **Main Responsibilities**

- ❖ Web application using CSS, HTML 5, Javascript
- ❖ Worked with co-developer to develop astonishing websites
- ❖ Followed policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times.

### **EDUCATION**

<ul> <li>Harvarde College of Science, Ogun-Nigeria Computer Science (HND)</li> </ul>	2022
• Allover Central Polytechnic, Sango Ota, Ogun State. Computer Science (OND)	2019
<ul> <li>State Senior High School, Oyewole, Lagos State National Examination Council (NECO).</li> </ul>	2014
• Uplifting Towers Nur/Pry School, Lagos State First School Leaving Certificate (F. S. L. C.)	2008

#### **CERTIFICATES OBTAINED WITH DATE**

•	Certificate in introduction to computers, Systems and Applications	2016
•	ICT Training	2017
•	Google Digital Skills	2019

# PERSONAL INTEREST

- Sports (Football)
- Travelling
- Listening to Music and Meeting People.

#### **REFEREES**

# Engr. Adeoba Adesuyi Dada

SIWES Department Supervisor Allover Central Polytechnic Sango, Ota Ogun State. 08022396381

# Mr. Ajani Ajibawo

CEO, Orelope Computer Center, Lagos State. Tel: 08062398386